https://zedaxis.com/privacy-policy/

×
Name *
Email *
CountryIndiaAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelauBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Saint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao S.A.R., ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Martin (Dutch part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSan MarinoSão Tomé and PríncipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia/Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited Kingdom (UK)United States (US)United States (US) Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVaticanVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (US)Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaSamoaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Phone *
Products/Services *---Zed SalesZed BillingZed SchemesZed ServiceZed AssetZed MobilityZed Power AnalyticsOthersMessage *
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice
The company respects the privacy and security of its users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our other users.
In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing the privacy practices for the entire company’s site. Here, you will learn about the types of information that we gather, how that information may be used, how we protect the information, and your options and rights related to such information and uses.
Information Collection and Use
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by the company.
The company is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The company may collect two types of information that users submit: public and private. The company defines Private information to be any information that allows others to contact a user or allows the collection of information about the user other than what is displayed on the site. Public information is information that may be displayed on the site, but cannot be linked to a particular user.
How We Protect Your Information
The privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. The company does not make PII available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding your company usage are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.
The company maintains practices and procedures designed to ensure the security, integrity and confidentiality of personal information collection through the Sites. A firewall protects the e-mail server to which all personal information is delivered. Access to the information is limited to those employees and contractors who need it to carry out their business functions. The company’s employees are educated about the importance of safeguarding personal information and preventing unauthorized access, disclosure and use. Finally, we use secure server software (“SSL”) that encrypts credit card information (including your name and address) submitted to the Site. This encryption protects this information so it cannot be viewed as it is transmitted over the Internet
Your access to some services and content is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. The company will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your user name and password to others. In addition, if applicable, you should remember to sign out of your company’s account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your PII correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that the company is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Notification of Changes
To ensure accuracy and security, the company reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how the company collects and uses personal information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the company Privacy Policy link so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Clients
Testimonials
Over the last 2 years we have been using distribution management system (Zed-Sales). The reports generated by this system have been a great help in our decision making process and planning.
We are in process of subscribing the Zed-Mobility products to empower the field force.
Kamal Malhotra
DGM- Sales Operations,Planning & Distribution ( MBG div.)
Motorola Mobility (a Lenovo Company)
Over the last 4 years, we have been using Zed-Service and have recently also started using Zed-Mobility products. The team at Zed-Axis keep themselves abreast with the latest developments in technology and incorporate the same in their solutions.
Prakash Mishra
AGM-IT Ram Ratna Global.
The Mobile handset business is a fast-changing environment and requires dashboard visibility on the real time basis. Zed Sales (Distribution management system) from Zed-Axis is quite powerful tool which we are using.
Zed Service is backbone of our after sales service ,enabling us to manage vast network of more than 1000 service centers.
Zed Axis provides seamless integration with systems like Microsoft AX and other third-party systems.
Rajan Jha
CIO- Jaina India Pvt. Ltd. (Karbonn, Gionee & Sansui)
Looking at the successful implementation of Zed-Sales and Zed-Service in India, we implemented the same in Nigeria, Egypt, Nepal, Myanmar and Indonesia. Zed-Axis team also helped on local language adaptation of their solutions making it easy for the local teams.
Jason He (HE YUAN)
Shenzhen Gionee Communication Equipment Co., Ltd
Happy to get associated with Zed-Axis. DMS (Distributor management system) is an end-to-end software solution designed specifically for the emerging and developing markets. It supports all our sales channels, all delivery models; it’s a user-friendly application that covers the complete down-stream supply chain, streamlines inventory, sales processes and distributor claims. Accurate and reliable data can be fetched out through DMS. We get a satisfactory support from Zed-Axis and all our issues or concerns are well handled by them.
Gauransh Chawla
Lemon Electronics Ltd.
“We’ve been users of Zed-Axis software solution for quite a while and it is really a needful system, it helps our business to track work orders for our technical support lab.
Service is really good in regards developing new things; tech support fixes issues in a really short time.”
Abraham Esses
Mobo – Mexicon
Zed Axis’s Solution is helping a lot in our service network, earlier when we didn’t have your system, we were struggling in real-time data management, service claims collections, approvals, invoicing, making reports, etc.
Now just with a click of the mouse, we can generate the real-time reports. Response from Zed-Axis team.
Pradeep Chugh
Fly Phones Russia
Zed Service application is helping us in managing over all service operations efficiently.
There is good support from Zed axis team all the times.
Jayachandra Naidu A
Head-Service Operations (HUPS)
Amara Raja Batteries Limited, Hyderabad.
Awards & Certification
Industries We Serve
Computer Peripherals
Home Appliances
Equipment Maintenance
Computer Hardware And Networking
FMCG
Request For Free Trial
Name *
Email *
CountryIndiaAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelauBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Saint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao S.A.R., ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Martin (Dutch part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSan MarinoSão Tomé and PríncipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia/Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited Kingdom (UK)United States (US)United States (US) Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVaticanVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (US)Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaSamoaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Phone *
Products/Services *---Zed SalesZed BillingZed SchemesZed ServiceZed AssetZed MobilityZed Power AnalyticsOthers
Message *
CLOSE
